Guide to the Cornell University Vice President for Public Affairs records, 1960-1979.
Cornell University Vice President for Public Affairs records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Vice President for Public Affairs records, 1960-1979.
4-3-1451
Cornell University. Vice President for Public Affairs.
11 cubic feet.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes records of state and national college and university associations; American Council on Education and other education organizations; Cornell programs, events, departments, and divisions; Cornell Center for International Studies; Cornell committees, commissions, councils, etc.; budgets; R.O.T.C.; students, including campus unrest, 1970; possible Cornell-C.I.A. connections; annual reports; Public Affairs Cabinet notes; Public Affairs Workshop materials; and related records of the Cornell Vice President for Public Affairs; includes files of Steven Muller. Also, a phonodisc of a training program panel, 1960.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes records of state and national college and university associations; American Council on Education and other education organizations; Cornell programs, events, departments, and divisions; Cornell Center for International Studies; Cornell committees, commissions, councils, etc.; budgets; R.O.T.C.; students, including campus unrest, 1970; possible Cornell-C.I.A. connections; annual reports; Public Affairs Cabinet notes; Public Affairs Workshop materials; and related records of the Cornell Vice President for Public Affairs; includes files of Steven Muller. Also, a phonodisc of a training program panel, 1960.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Muller, Steven, 1927-2013.; Muller, Steven, 1927-2013; Cornell University -- Administration.; Cornell University -- Public relations.; Cornell University -- Students.; United States. Central Intelligence Agency.; Cornell University; United States. Central Intelligence Agency
Subjects:
Education -- Societies, etc.; College students -- Political activity -- Ithaca.; College students -- Political activity; Education -- Societies, etc.; Management; Public relations; Students
Places:
New York (State) -- Ithaca
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- A - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- American Council on Education (Box 1)
- American Association of State Colleges and Universities - campus crisis (Box 1)
- ACE - Commission on International Education, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
- ACE - Policy and Planning Committee (Box 1)
- ACE - Presidents' Institutes and Business Officers Institutes (Box 1)
- Associations of American Universities (Box 1)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of New York State (Box 1)
- B - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- C - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Center for Advanced Intercultural Studies (CAIS) (formerly The Bridge) (Box 1)
- Center for the Arts at Ithaca Correspondence, etc., 1966-1971 (Box 1)
- Center for the Arts at Ithaca Executive Committee Minutes, 1966-1970 (Box 1)
- Center for the Arts at Ithaca Financial Material (Box 1)
- Consultants (Box 2)
- Constitutional Convention - NYS (2 folders), 1967 (Box 2)
- CU Ad Hoc Judiciary Committee (Long) (Box 2)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1968-11-1971-01 (Box 2)
- CAL, 1968-10-1968-11 (Box 2)
- CAL, 1968-04-1968-09 (Box 2)
- CAL, 1967-08-1968-04 (Box 2)
- CAL, 1966-10-1967-07 (Box 2)
- CAL, 1963-02-1966-09 (Box 2)
- Cornell Club of New York (Box 2)
- Cornell Daily Sun (Box 2)
- Cornell Newsletter (Box 2)
- CU Academic Program -- miscellaneous (Box 2)
- CU Administrative Reorganization (Box 2)
- CU Admissions Office (Box 2)
- CU Africana Studies and Research Center (2 folders) (Box 2)
- CU Agriculture, College of (Box 2)
- CU Alumni Affairs: Committee on Alumni Trustee Nominations (Box 3)
- CU Architecture, College of (Box 3)
- CU Arts and Sciences, College of (4 folders) (Box 3)
- CU Assistant to President for Alumni Relations (Hunt Bradley) (Box 3)
- CU Assistant to the President - NYC (4 folders) (Box 3)
- CU Assistant to President - NYC - Office Space, Lease, Furnishings, Personnel matters (Box 3)
- CU Biological Sciences Division (Box 3)
- CU Black Graduate Students (Box 3)
- CU Budget Office (2 folders) (Box 3)
- CU Budget Office - reports (Box 3)
- CU Buildings and Properties (Box 3)
- CU Business and Public Administration School (Box 3)
- CU Business Intern Program (Summer Intern Program) (Box 3)
- CU Business Intern Program (Summer Intern Program) (Box 4)
- CU Campus Unrest, 1969 (Box 4)
- CU Centennial Report (Box 4)
- CU Center for Educational Research and Development (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies, 1962-1967 (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies Area Programs (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies Budget (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies Defense and Disarmament Workshop, 1970-08 (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies Executive Committee, 1968-02-1970-02 (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies Executive Committee, 1963-04-1968-02 (Box 4)
- CU Center for International Studies Overseas Operations Committee (Box 4)
- CU Citizenship Recess (Box 4)
- CU and Civil Rights (Box 4)
- CU Commencement (Box 4)
- CU Commission on the Interdependence of University Regulations and Local, State and Federal Law (Sindler.com), 1967-09 (Box 4)
- CU Commission on Residential Environment (Saperston Com.), 1967 (Box 4)
- CU Comission on Undergraduate Education (Box 4)
- CU Computer Services (Box 4)
- CU Constituent Assembly (Box 5)
- CU Controller's Office (Box 5)
- CU Cornell in Perspective Program (Box 5)
- CU Cornell United Religious Work (Box 5)
- CU COSEP Program (Box 5)
- CU Counsel (Box 5)
- CU Dean of Students and "America is Hard to Find" Concert (Box 5)
- CU Engineering, College of (Box 5)
- CU Education, School of (Box 5)
- CU Faculty Committee on Public Affairs (Box 5)
- CU Faculty Reorganization (Box 5)
- CU Future Plans (Box 5)
- CU Government Department (Box 5)
- CU Government 104 (S. Muller course) (Box 5)
- CU Housing and Dining, including University Unions (Box 5)
- CU Industrial and Labor Relations, New York State School of (Box 5)
- CU Investments and Public Policy Commission (Marcham), 1968 (Box 5)
- CU Latin America Year (Box 5)
- CU Libraries (Box 5)
- CU Music, Department of including Glee Club, Univ. Orchestra (Box 5)
- CU New York City Programs (Box 5)
- CU Organization of Public Affairs offices, 1964 (Box 5)
- CU Parking Problems (Box 5)
- CU Physical Education and Athletics (Box 5)
- CU President's Commission on Student Involvement in Decision-Making (Morison Commission), 1969-05 (Box 5)
- CU President Corson, 1970-09-1971-04 (Box 5)
- CU President Corson, 1969-09-1970-09 (Box 5)
- CU President Perkins, 1966-02-1967-05 (Box 5)
- CU President Perkins, 1967-05-1968-08 (Box 6)
- CU President Perkins, 1968-09-1969-08 (Box 6)
- CU President Perkins Financial Report and Rusk Visit (Box 6)
- CU President Perkins' Resignation; Investiture of President Corson (Box 6)
- CU Press (Box 6)
- CU Professional Skills Roster (Box 6)
- CU Provost (Box 6)
- CU Public Affairs Budget Problems (Box 6)
- CU Public Affairs Budget Working Papers, 1964-1967 (Box 6)
- CU Public Affairs Budget Working Papers, 1967-1969 (Box 6)
- CU Public Affairs Budget Working Papers, 1969-1971 (Box 6)
- CU Public Affairs Data Services (3 folders) (Box 6)
- CU Public Affairs Meetings and Mailings (2 folders) (Box 6)
- CU Public Information Office (Box 6)
- CU Public Information Office (Box 7)
- CU Public Information - Chronicle correspondence (Box 7)
- CU Public Information - News Section (2 folders) (Box 7)
- CU Public Information - Radio and Television (2 folders) (Box 7)
- CU Public Information - Visual Services (Box 7)
- CU Publications Office (2 folders) (Box 7)
- CU Publications Office - Budget matters, Announcements, Annual Reports and President's Reports (Box 7)
- CU Radiophysics and Space Research, Center for (Box 7)
- CU Registrar (Box 7)
- CU Research Park -- TCAD - FIPD (Box 7)
- CU ROTC (Box 7)
- CU Science, Technology and Society (Box 7)
- CU Special Events Office (Box 7)
- CU Special Trustee Committee on Campus Unrest at Cornell (Box 7)
- CU Spring (3 folders), 1969 (Box 7)
- CU Students - various miscellaneous items, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
- CU Student Briefings, 1966 (Box 8)
- CU Student Demonstration, 1958-05 (Box 8)
- CU Student Government (Box 8)
- CU Treasurer's Office (Box 8)
- CU Trustee Housing Committee (Box 8)
- CU Veterinary College (Box 8)
- CU Vice President for Academic Affairs (Box 8)
- CU Vice President for Business (Box 8)
- CU Vice President for Planning (Box 8)
- CU Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies (Box 8)
- CU Vice President for Social and Environmental Studies (Box 8)
- CU Vice President for Student Affairs (Box 8)
- CU Vice Provost (Box 8)
- CU Vietnam Discussion Group (Box 8)
- CU Williams Commission, 1968-04 (Box 8)
- D - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 8)
- Education and World Affairs (EWA) (Box 8)
- EWA - Committee on University International Programs (CUIP) (Box 8)
- EWA - HEW Conference on the Study of Federal Programs in International Education, 1968-09 (Box 8)
- EWA Study of Professional Schools (Box 8)
- F - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- Foreign Assistance Act of 1966, 1966 (Box 9)
- Gemmell, Edgar M. (consultant to Cornell University) (Box 9)
- G - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- H - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- Higher Education Act of 1965, 1965 (Box 9)
- Higher Education Act of 1965, 1965 (Box 9)
- I - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- International Conference on the World Crisis in Ed. (3), 1967-10 (Box 9)
- International Education Act (2 folders) (Box 9)
- Tom Jones (Box 9)
- K - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- Lehman, Herbert H. Graduate Fellowships (Box 9)
- Liberal Arts Colleges, Study of Future (Box 9)
- Littel, Edward G. (Box 9)
- M - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- N - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- P - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- NY Coordinating Council on Foreign Area Studies (Box 9)
- NEW YORK TIMES Correspondence (Box 9)
- S - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 9)
- Seven Universities Group (Box 9)
- SM - Congratulatory letters on becoming Cornell's VPPA (Box 9)
- Turin Center -- Cornell-ILO Agreement (Box 9)
- U.S. Department of State (Box 9)
- U.S. House of Representatives (Box 9)
- U.S. Senate (Box 10)
- W - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 10)
- WVBR (Box 10)
- Yugoslavia (4 folders) (Box 10)
- S. Muller speeches and articles (2 folders), 1966-1968, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
- Public Affairs Workshop (7 folders), 1970-1976 (Box 11)
- Public Affairs Annual reports (14 folders), 1964-1979 (Box 11)
- PAC Notes (9 folders), 1971-1979 (Box 11)